♪ ♪
♪ WATCH IT! ♪
♪ I WAS BORN IN A
CROSSFIRE HURRICANE ♪
♪ ♪
♪ AND I HOWLED AT MY MA
IN THE DRIVING RAIN ♪
♪ ♪
♪ BUT ITS ALL RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ IN FACT, ITS A GAS! ♪
♪ BUT ITS ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ IM JUMPIN JACK FLASH ♪
♪ ITS A GAS! GAS! GAS! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I WAS RAISED BY A
TOOTHLESS, BEARDED HAG ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I WAS SCHOOLED WITH A
STRAP RIGHT ACROSS MY BACK ♪
♪ ♪
♪ BUT ITS ALL RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ IN FACT, ITS A GAS! ♪
♪ BUT ITS ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ IM JUMPIN JACK FLASH ♪
♪ ITS A GAS! GAS! GAS! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ I WAS DROWNED, I WAS WASHED
UP AND LEFT FOR DEAD ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I FELL DOWN TO MY FEET
AND I SAW THEY BLED ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I FROWNED AT THE CRUMBS
OF A CRUST OF BREAD ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I WAS CROWNED WITH A
SPIKE RIGHT THRU MY HEAD ♪
♪ AH, AH YEAH ♪
♪ BUT ITS ALL RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ IN FACT, ITS A GAS! ♪
♪ BUT ITS ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ IM JUMPIN JACK FLASH ♪
♪ ITS A GAS! GAS! GAS! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ JUMPIN JACK FLASH,
ITS A GAS! ♪
♪ ♪